I've always wanted to start a business that not only made money or grew, but also more
importantly added value to the planet.
A trailblazer is someone who only cares about one thing and that is pursuing their passion.
And when we started 10 years ago, selling ugly fruits and vegetables online was a crazy
idea.
Hungry Harvest is on a mission to fight food waste and fight hunger.
What we do is we source produce that otherwise would go to waste because it's odd size or
shape, all perfectly fresh, perfectly nutritious, and we sell it via e-commerce.
When customers sign up for Hungry Harvest, they're reducing food waste, they're helping
subsidized produce and other food for folks that are living in food deserts, and they're
helping invest in the local economy.
In my opinion, we're just getting started.
For every trailblazer, they've never really reached their end goal.
It's always kind of a pursuit and journey.
I'm Evan Lutz.
I'm the CEO and founder of Hungry Harvest, and I'm a University of Maryland graduate.
Go Turks!